DREAM is a Qwen Cloud MemoryAgent for source-backed engineering intelligence.
Engineering context is scattered across tickets, runbooks, code, incidents, PRs, and past decisions.
The architecture uses Qwen Cloud generation, governed memory, FastAPI, and Alibaba Function Compute packaging.
Memory Hub makes source intake, parsed sections, review state, and evidence coverage visible.
Knowledge intake promotes reviewed source cards and quarantines stale or unsafe claims.
Retrieval traces show why docs, incidents, code, tests, Jira items, and PRs were selected.
DREAM turns retrieved memory into questions, impact maps, engineering briefs, and Jira-ready drafts.
Audit and evaluation loops capture scores, source coverage, warnings, and human ratings.
DREAM turns scattered engineering context into persistent memory.
Memory Hub keeps source intake, parsed sections, review state, and evidence visible.
Knowledge intake promotes only reviewed source cards into reusable memory.
Retrieval paths explain why docs, incidents, code, tests, Jira, and PRs were selected.
Requirement workflows turn retrieved memory into review-ready Jira drafts.
Runtime settings expose backend mode before local or Alibaba Cloud execution.
The proof chain validates Qwen config, Alibaba deployment files, CI, video, backend health, and final readiness gates.
DREAM remembers source truth, retrieves evidence, generates with Qwen Cloud, and proves deployment on Alibaba Cloud.