I changed a rollout from ten percent to twenty.
The scary part?
An agent can confidently bring back the old answer.
In production, stale truth is worse than no memory.
So I built DREAM.
Qwen understands what experience means; deterministic lifecycle rules decide what can come back.
This is the public build.
It is running in Singapore, on Alibaba Function Compute.
First, I set the canary at ten percent, for thirty minutes.
Qwen recognizes the preference.
It gives me an inspectable receipt.
Then I change it to twenty percent for forty-five minutes.
Qwen catches the conflict; DREAM keeps only the new value active.
In a fresh session, DREAM returns twenty percent in nineteen of sixty-four tokens.
The old instruction never enters context.
The test I cared about was persistence.
I saved a Qwen-curated memory, rebuilt the same source, and forced a new Function Compute instance.
The instance ID changed; the memory, decision, and Qwen receipt did not.
Twenty simultaneous conflicting writes also succeeded, leaving one active truth and nineteen historical versions.
In a clearly labeled synthetic evaluation, the same Qwen model improved from 25.3 to 48.7 across seven paired cases.
A separate twenty-four-case lifecycle suite passed every recall, stale-leak, and token-budget check.
Underneath: Angular and FastAPI on Function Compute; Qwen Cloud for meaning;
Tablestore transactions for one current truth; and temporary credentials from a narrow RAM role.
I do not want longer history.
I want one current, reviewable truth, for the next decision.